A new co
worker started three
months ago Let's
call her Linda
She seems pretty
nice which is
why I'm really
not sure about
all this At
my work we
have a tradition
where once a
new employee successfully
completes their probation
we go out
for a team
lunch Nothing fancy
but something nice
to celebrate Linda
passed her probation
so we went
out for lunch
As we're eating
we all get
to talking and
the topic of
the magic of
pregnancy childbirth comes
up Everyone was
sharing sweet moments
from their pregnancy
I enthusiastically joined
in but didn't
share any of
my own I
think Linda noticed
because she specifically
turned to me
and said Linda
you had twins
didn't you That
must have been
a wonderful experience
I smiled and
said something along
the lines of
how I wished
my pregnancy and
birth had been
as positive an
experience as theirs
had been To
be clear it
was not said
sarcastically at all
The truth is
I hated every
moment of being
pregnant I could
write a long
list of all
the magical symptoms
I had but
I'll just give
you the highlights
Horrific vivid nightmares
hyperemesis gravidarum severe
morning sickness debilitating
migraines a metallic
taste in my
mouth and then
the birth Honestly
I feel like
anything that could
go wrong but
not be life
threatening did go
wrong Worst of
all due to
some of the
first few days
with my girls
It's safe to
say I hated
every moment of
being pregnant and
labor It was
not a magical
experience by any
stretch of the
imagination I didn't
say any of
this to Linda
I just responded
as I mentioned
After my reply
Linda started getting
short with me
Later I asked
her privately what
was going on
She snapped and
told me what
I said was
insensitive and undermined
their experiences and
told me I
was an a
hole for it
Since then she's
sort of cooled
off and is
less hostile or
at least less
openly hostile but
last week she
invited all the
girls in the
team to a
ladies night Everyone
but me Now
I don't mind
so much since
ladies nights are
not really my
thing but the
fact that she
pointedly excluded me
has made things
awkward I feel
like I need
to do something
I'm not really
in the mood
for drama I
have enough of
that in my
life right now
I don't need
more so I
haven't confronted her
about it yet
And as I
said she is
otherwise a really
nice person normally
pretty friendly and
easy going So
I'm left wondering
if I really
was an a
hole Was what
I said insensitive
did it undermine
their experience Before
I ask her
about it I
could use some
perspective because I
honestly just don't
know Aida