Title The Pregnant Paws Disaster
at Lunch Scene Office Cafeteria
The team is gathered around
a large table celebrating Linda's
successful probation Plates of food
and drinks are spread out
Laughter fills the air as
everyone shares stories Narrator So
three months ago we had
a new co worker join
us Let's call her Linda
Linda seemed nice enough like
the kind of person who
always has gum and shares
it So naturally I wasn't
sure what to make of
what happened next Narrator We
have this team tradition When
a new employee survives the
probation period we celebrate with
a team lunch It's usually
something nice but wallet friendly
because let's be honest corporate
budgets don't exactly scream extravagant
Linda breezed through her probation
like a pro so we
head out for lunch Things
start off casual like a
scene from a sitcom where
everyone's having a great time
Camera pans to the group
eating chatting and laughing Narrator
And then oh boy the
topic of the magic of
pregnancy childbirth came up Cue
the Kodak moments and Hallmark
card sentiments Everyone was sharing
sweet baby bump tales think
glowing not imploding I joined
in enthusiastically nodding like a
bobblehead but keeping mum about
my own experience Linda Turns
to me eyes sparkling you
had twins didn't you That
must have been a double
dose of wonderful Narrator I
smile thinking if only she
knew So I say something
along the lines of how
I wished my pregnancy and
birth had been as positive
as theirs I swear it
wasn't dripping with sarcasm but
on the inside all I
could think was cut to
a comically exaggerated dream sequence
The narrator is a pregnant
woman dealing with dramatic horrific
symptoms Nightmares featuring giant vegetables
rivers of morning sickness and
migraines that throb to the
beat of we will rock
you Narrator To summarize my
pregnancy was like if Stephen
King directed a rom com
Back to lunch scene the
narrator's face now visibly strained
but still smiling Narrator Now
if I'd really unleashed the
horror story I doubt there'd
have been any celebratory ice
cream cones left unscarred So
I kept it simple But
Linda bless her reactionary heart
seemed to bristle Linda Her
demeanor shifts slightly tone icy
really That's unfortunate narrator After
the lunch I pull Linda
aside and in my best
trying to be diplomatic but
totally confused voice ask her
what's wrong Instead of unloading
some psychological thriller level motive
she calls me insensitive According
to her my little comment
had apparently undermined their beautiful
motherhood experiences qualifying me as
the office a hole Cut
to comedic montage Narrator attempting
everyday tasks while horrifying pregnancy
flashbacks distract her ultimately screwing
up each task in slapstick
style Narrator Now she's cooled
off a bit Think lukewarm
tea but last week she
organized a night And guess
who didn't make the invite
list Yours truly Not that
I live for these gatherings
but the exclusion had awkward
written all over it The
vibe in the office Might
as well be an episode
of The Office post Michael
Scott Narrator Drama is the
last thing I need My
life could already star in
a daytime soap So I
haven't confronted her about it
I mean Linda's generally nice
the type to ask how
your cat's doing remember the
cat's name and genuinely care
about the answer So the
burning question remains Was I
really an a hole Did
my honesty clash with the
fairy tale narrative too harshly
Before I approach her I
need some perspective Seriously Aida
Scene fades as the narrator
looks around with a puzzled
and thoughtful expression while the
team chatters on The end